

ONDREJ PITOŇÁK

Junior Web Developer

Poprad, Slovakia

+421 917 408 195

ondrejpit@gmail.com

△ Skills

Web Development

	=
JavaScript	****
Typescript	****
HTML 5	★★★★☆
CSS 3	★★★☆☆
Angular 2+	★★★☆☆
jQuery	★★★☆☆
Bootstrap	★★★☆☆
Material Design	★★☆☆☆
NodeJS	★★★☆☆
PHP	★★☆☆☆
AngularJS	★☆☆☆☆

Programming Languages

Python	★★☆☆☆
Java	★☆☆☆☆

Databases

PostgreSQL	$\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \Delta \Delta$
ElasticSearch	$\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \Diamond \Diamond$

Other

Other	
Docker	★★☆☆☆
CI/CD	★★☆☆☆
GIT	★★★☆☆
Gitlab	★★★☆☆
JIRA	$\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \Diamond \Diamond$
Visual Studio Code	$\star\star\star\star$
IntelliJ IDEA	★★★☆☆
Firebase	$\star\star\star \Delta \Delta \Delta$
MS Office	★★★☆☆



Just graduated programmer with more then 2 years of experience. Skilled at full stack web development using modern languages, libraries and technologies. Valuable for the ability to quickly suggest and evaluate various programming and design solutions. Praised for willingness to share experience. Seeking exciting and educational opportunities in frontend or full stack web development to grow as a professional.

Education

Master Degree in Computer Science (2017 - 2020)

Faculty of Informatics and Information Technologies Slovak University of Technology

Bachelor Degree in Informatics (2014 - 2017)

Faculty of Informatics and Information Technologies Slovak University of Technology

Work Experience –

Junior Full Stack Developer (08/2019 - 04/2020)

ARTIN Solutions, s. r. o.

- Configuration and development of new features in the application for insurance agents used in several european countries (plain JS, AngularJS, Spring Boot, JPA, MySQL, MS SQL)
- MS SQL migrations
- Communication with customer in English

Trainee Frontend Developer (10/2017 - 07/2019)

SOFTEC, spol. s r.o.

- Development of interactive graphical web applications (Angular 2+, D3.js, NodeJS, ElasticSearch, CI/CD)
- Development of a responsive UI for a financial consulting company (Angular 2+, Material Design)
- Development of an internal system for employee benefits (Angular 2+, Bootstrap)
- Integration of the page with the Exponea interface (jQuery, Exponea API)
- CI/CD

(Jenkins, Docker and DCOS)

• Development of various prototypes for potential customers